let DummyData = [
  {
   "questionId":"1",
   "question":"Which player has maximum number of one day ducks?",
   "options":['Wasim Akram','Romesh Kaluwitharana','Inzamam-ul-Haq','Sanath Jayasuriya'],
   "correctAnswer":"Sanath Jayasuriya",
 },
 {
   "questionId":"2",
   "question":"Which player has scored the fastest century?",
   "options":['Coery Anderson','Mark Boucher','Brian Larad','Shahid Afridi'],
   "correctAnswer":"Coery Anderson",
 },
 {
   "questionId":"3",
   "question":"Who is having the best one day bowling figures?",
   "options":['Muttiah Muralitharan', 'Anil Kumble', 'Chaminda Vaas', "Glenn McGrath"],
   "correctAnswer":"Chaminda Vaas",
 },
 {
   "questionId":"4",
   "question":"Who was the first player to score a One Day International century?",
   "options":['Dennis Amiss','Derek Randall','Don Bradman','Mike Denniss'],
   "correctAnswer":"Dennis Amiss",
 },
 {
   "questionId":"5",
   "question":"When did South Africa made its One Day International debut?",
   "options":['1971','1991','1994','1980'],
   "correctAnswer":"1991",
 },
 {
   "questionId":"6",
   "question":"In which year did India make its One Day International debut?",
   "options":['1971','1974','1973','1974'],
   "correctAnswer":"1974",
 },
 {
   "questionId":"7",
   "question":"Who hit the winning runs in Indiaâ€™s famous NatWest final victory against England in 2002?",
   "options":['Zaheer Khan','Harbhajan Singh','Mohammed Kaif','Yuvaraj Singh'],
   "correctAnswer":"Zaheer Khan",
 },
 {
   "questionId":"8",
   "question":"How many matches did it take for Sachin Tendulkar to score his first one day hundred?",
   "options":['74','79','94','84'],
   "correctAnswer":"79",
 },
 {
   "questionId":"9",
   "question":"Against which team did India win its first One Day International match?",
   "options":['England','Pakistan','South Africa','East Africa'],
   "correctAnswer":"East Africa",
 },
 {
   "questionId":"10",
   "question":"How many one day wickets did Kapil Dev capture?",
   "options":['253','256','261','157'],
   "correctAnswer":"253",
 }
]

export {DummyData}
